{
    "introduction":"Welcome Admin! Take the quiz about Java!", 
    "questions":[
        {"question":"True or False: Java is a strongly typed language.", 
         "answers":["True","False"],
         "correct":1},
        {"question":"In Java Strings are primitive types.", 
         "answers":["True","False"],
         "correct":1},
        {"question":"How many primitive data types are there in Java?", 
         "answers":["6","7","8","9"],
         "correct":3},
         {"question":"In Java byte, short, int and long all of these are", 
         "answers":["signed","unsigned","Both of the above","None of the above"],
         "correct":1},
         {"question":"Size of int in Java is", 
         "answers":["16 bit","32 bit","64 bit","Depends on execution environment"],
         "correct":2},
          {"question":"The smallest integer type is ......... and its size is ......... bits.", 
         "answers":["short, 8","byte, 8","short, 16","Byte, 32"],
         "correct":2},
          {"question":"Size of float and double in Java is", 
         "answers":["32 and 64","64 and 64","32 and 32","64 and 32"],
         "correct":1},
         {"question":"Automatic type conversion in Java takes place when", 
         "answers":["Two type are compatible and size of destination type is shorter than source type.","Two type are compatible and size of destination type is equal of source type.","Two type are compatible and size of destination type is larger than source type.","All of the above"],
         "correct":3},
         {"question":"Which of the following automatic type conversion will be possible?", 
         "answers":["short to int","byte to int","int to long","long to int"],
         "correct":3},
           {"question":"Which of the following is correct?", 
         "answers":["jQuery is a JavaScript Library","jQuery is a JSON Library"],
         "correct":1},
         {"question":"jQuery uses CSS selectors and XPath expressions to select elements?", 
         "answers":["True","False"],
         "correct":1},
         {"question":"Which sign does jQuery use as a shortcut for jQuery?", 
         "answers":["$ sign","% sign","? sign"],
         "correct":1},
          {"question":"Is jQuery a W3C standard?", 
         "answers":["Yes","No"],
         "correct":2},
          {"question":"$(“span”). What does it select?", 
         "answers":["All span elements","The first span element"],
         "correct":1},
         {"question":"Is jQuery a library for client scripting or server scripting?", 
         "answers":["Client scripting"," Server scripting"],
         "correct":1},
         {"question":"Is it possible to use jQuery together with AJAX?", 
         "answers":["Yes","No"],
         "correct":1},
         {"question":"The jQuery html() method works for both HTML and XML documents", 
         "answers":["True"," False"],
         "correct":2},
         {"question":"Is it possible to use jQuery together with AJAX?", 
         "answers":["$(“span”).style(“background-color”,”blue”);","$(“span”).manipulate(“background-color”,”blue”);","$(“span”).css(“background-color”,”blue”);","$(“span”).layout(“background-color”,”blue”);"],
         "correct":3},
         {"question":"jQuery method to hide selected elements?", 
         "answers":["visible(false)","hidden()","display(none)","hide()"],
         "correct":4},
         {"question":" jQuery method to set one or more style properties for selected elements?", 
         "answers":["style()","css()","html()"],
         "correct":2}
    ]
}